Justin Rajewski

rajewskijustin@gmail.com • Los Angeles, CA 90028

https://www.linkedin.com/in/justinrajewski89/

(815)207-1952

GitHub: github.com/justinraj89 Portfolio Website: <u>Justin Rajewski</u>

Software Engineer (Frontend)

Frontend & Backend Engineering | User Interface | Quality Assurance

Knowledgeable and self-driven Software Engineer with a passion for developing innovative programs that expedite the efficiency and effectiveness of professional organizational success. Well-versed in technology and writing code to create systems that are reliable, robust, and user-friendly. High achieving, hard working, and collaborative team player. Recently completed an immersive bootcamp training course and seeking a full time software engineering position on a team.

Skills

- React/JS
- HTML/CSS
- Javascript
- Redux
- Diango/Python
- Next JS

- MongoDB
- PostgreSQL
- REST APIs
- Postman
- Heroku and AWS (S3, EC2)
- Jira/Confluence

- Scrum
- Quality Assurance
- Team Building & Leadership
- Tailwind CSS
- UX/UI
- Bootstrap

Software Engineering Projects

General Assembly, Los Angeles, CA

Software Engineering Immersive Course

July - October 2022

Attended an intense bootcamp course to improve my frontend and full stack engineering skills. Focused on fundamentals, JS/HTML/CSS and various frameworks/libraries including React, Express, and Django. Delivered projects with deadlines in a team environment.

Moovie - https://github.com/justinraj89/Moovie

Technologies Used: Node JS, Express, MongoDB, Mongoose, React JS, Bootstrap, JWT, Bcrypt, TMDB (3rd party API).

- Moovie is a MERN stack application that allows users to create an account, login, and build their own custom watchlists. All movie data is pulled from TMDB (3rd party API) This application is fully responsive and provides a pleasant user experience whether mobile or desktop.

Doodle-Gram - https://github.com/justinraj89/Doodle-Gram

Technologies Used: Node JS, Express, MongoDB, EJS, Passport, Google Oauth

- Doodle-Gram is an Instagram-type full stack CRUD application. Users can login using their Google accounts, browse a collection of posted artwork, add their own artwork, comment, edit and delete posts. This application is fully responsive and was built with a mobile first mentality.

Beastcoast Memes - https://github.com/justinraj89/Beastcoast-Memes

Technologies Used: Django, Python, PostgreSQL, Bootstrap, CSRF token

 Group project built with a team of 4 people from my General Assembly cohort. My role on this project was the Lead Designer, along with Database Manager. This project was our first real taste of how to use the proper Git workflow.

War - https://github.com/justinraj89/War

Technologies Used: HTML, CSS, Javascript

- Browser game created using vanilla Javascript, MVC architecture.

Career Experience

Standard Timed Text LLC, Los Angeles, CA **Software Engineering Consultant**

March 2020 - Present

Technical Scope: React, JavaScript, NodeJS, Python, Django, PostgreSQL, AWS

Maintained applications which allow STT customers and linguists the ability to submit and take work orders as well as providing a dashboard for management. Web-based application communicates with external systems used for order tracking and invoicing.

- React JS application with Django CMS for quote requests, order submission, and job management tasks.
- Worked on feature requests, bug fixes, and maintained the production environment.

Duclos Lenses, Chatsworth, CA **Lens Repair Technician**

Oct 2021 - July 2022

Performed repairs, and calibrated high end cinema camera lenses at a globally recognized lens repair facility responsible for servicing state-of-the art lenses and systems for major production studios.

- Cultivated an understanding of the service and assembly of the most complex lens systems in the industry requiring the highest level of attention to detail and documentation.
- Developed the skills and practices (both personal and technical,) required to deliver the highest level of service while adhering to strict deadlines.

Industry Camera, Burbank, CA Lens Service Technician Lead

July 2019 - Oct 2021

Led lens service department at a camera equipment rental company. Inspected all incoming lenses returned from rentals and reported and logged any damages found. Transitioned to a role of conducting specialized repairs of high value lenses in addition to maintenance and calibration.

- Developed capabilities to repair and service camera electronics in addition to lenses in order to meet required 48hr turn time of equipment inspections.
- Grew the department and house capabilities by onboarding and training additional lens and camera technicians.

The Camera Division, North Hollywood, CA

Aug 2014 - July 2019

Lens Service Technician

Lens Service Technician for a studio rental house. Inspected all incoming lenses, cinema cameras, and accessories upon completion of lease. Developed a strong understanding of how to calibrate equipment using sophisticated test equipment.

- Acted as lead technician responsible for service and calibration of professional grade video camera lenses and equipment leased to customers.
- Achieved training and certification of specialized tools and systems including Leica lenses, Zeiss lenses, collimators, projectors and instruments used for precision lens and camera adjustments.
- Developed strong relationships with clients by providing personal consultations, answering technical questions, and assisting with customized adjustments.

Additional Experience

Electronics Technician/Quality Assurance Lead - Sennco Solutions, Plainfield, IL (2011 - 2014)

Education

Certificate in Software Engineering - General Assembly, Los Angeles CA (2022)